hey guys I want to show you something
really cool about the Pythagorean
theorem you're probably familiar with A2
+ B2 = c^2 and here's a cool
visualization that shows it if you add
the areas of these two red squares it's
equal to the area of this blue square
but these don't have to be squares it
works for isos right triangles they
could be equilateral triangles they
could be regular pentagons they could
even be semicircles for each of these
the red areas add up to the blue area
and this can work for any similar figure
we could even look at something like the
state of orgon if we align the state of
organ along this side this side and this
side it'll be true that the sum of these
two red areas will equal the blue area
or other words a plus b is equal to C
how exciting